<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Women Tech Space</title>
    <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Women Tech Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 13:35:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://womentechspace.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Tech Space 2019</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/events/march2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/events/march2019/</guid>
      <description>We will be running the next Women Tech Space workshop on Saturday 23rd March 2019 at Puppet Belfast.
This will be a full day workshop running from 9.30am to 5pm.
As a workshop attendee you will:
 Create your first website and learn how you could complete and/or enhance it. Find out whether programming might be a career option for you. Meet people from the industry and learn more about programming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Women Tech Space Workshop</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/information/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 13:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/information/</guid>
      <description>We want women to experience what it is like to code and work with technology. Our goal is to create a safe environment where women can explore technology.
We are trans-inclusive and welcome all women from all walks of life. Men are welcome to attend as well. We don&amp;rsquo;t want men out of the IT industry, we just want more women in it.
If you are female or identify as female, you can apply for a pass!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 13:25:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/faq/</guid>
      <description>Do I need to know anything about websites or programming?
No! Workshops are for beginners. You don’t need to know anything about it. However, if you have a little bit of technical knowledge (i.e. you know what HTML or CSS are) you still can apply!
Should I bring my own laptop?
Yes. We have no hardware, so we expect you to bring your computer with you.
In the event that you cannot get your hands on a laptop, please get in touch as we do have links to a local community group that can help out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Previous Events</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/previous_events/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 13:28:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/previous_events/</guid>
      <description>This isn&amp;rsquo;t our first rodeo!
We have been running Django Girls workshops for a number of years and each time, have had a sell-out event.
In 2017, we decided to start a series of monthly workshops called Women Tech Space to provide a more regular slot to provide local women with the help and support they need to continue their coding journey.
Women Tech Space ran for a few years but since late 2018, we have taken a brief hiatus as life/work/children took over for a little while!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Django anyway?</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/what_is_django/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 13:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/about-us/what_is_django/</guid>
      <description>Django is a high-level Python Web framework that encourages rapid development and clean, pragmatic design. Built by experienced developers, it takes care of much of the hassle of Web development, so you can focus on writing your app without needing to reinvent the wheel. It’s free and open source.
If you are a beginner, this framework provides you with most of the tools and setup required to get a site up and running with minimal fuss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Write for us</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/blog/blog_for_us/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/blog/blog_for_us/</guid>
      <description>If you would like to write for Women Tech Space, get in touch at womentechspace@gmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a coach!</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/coaches/become/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 13:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/coaches/become/</guid>
      <description>We would be delighted if you would like to join us as a coach!
You don&amp;rsquo;t have to have been a coach before and we love previous attendees to return as coaches and mentor some of our newcomers. Don&amp;rsquo;t worry if you think you don&amp;rsquo;t have enough knowledge. We are all still learning and coaches will help each other out!
Coach submissions are open. Click here to become a Django Girls coach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/sponsors/become/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 13:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/sponsors/become/</guid>
      <description>We couldn&amp;rsquo;t be here without the support from amazing people and organisations who have donated money, knowledge and time to help us make this a reality
We have met some super people around Northern Ireland.
You are all awesome!
If you would like to become a sponsor or just get involved in any way, please get in touch.
Email us at: womentechspace@gmail.com and we can grab a coffee!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current coaches</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/coaches/list/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 13:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/coaches/list/</guid>
      <description>  Zoe Gadon-Thompson     Jen Hanratty     Danielle Topping   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Current sponsors!</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/sponsors/current/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jan 2019 13:15:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/sponsors/current/</guid>
      <description>More info soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Tech Space</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/blog/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/blog/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>The first ever Women Tech Space is scheduled for Monday 25th September 2017 at the Ormeau Baths gallery. We are sold out and we are hoping that we get 30 women full of motivation and drive to learn!
Women Tech Space was in discussion for a long time. I have been involved with Django Girls Belfast for a while now and each workshop becomes a little better, a little bit smoother, more relaxed and a lot of fun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Women Tech Space monthly</title>
      <link>https://womentechspace.github.io/events/monthly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:35:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womentechspace.github.io/events/monthly/</guid>
      <description>We have no upcoming events.
Please get in touch if you have any ideas for workshops you would like to attend or coach at. We are always open to suggestions!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>